Guide to the Program on Non-Profit Organizations, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Program on Non-Profit Organizations, Yale University, records
1973-2004
RU 950
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
57
566.19
The records consist of subject and personnel files, including computer files, of the Program on Non-Profit Organizations (PONPO) at Yale. The records document all aspects of the program including administration, research, and finance.
Yale University. Institution for Social and Policy Studies. Program on Non-Profit Organizations
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Yale School of Management, 2004.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Biographical / Historical
The Program on Non-Profit Organizations (PONPO) at Yale University was founded in 1978 to foster interdisciplinary research aimed at developing an understanding of nonprofit organizations and their role in economic and political life. Originally an initiative of Yale president Kingman Brewster, PONPO was first directed by Professor John G. Simon of the Law School in cooperation with Charles E. Lindblom of the Political Science and Economics Departments and director of the Institute for Social and Policy Studies. PONPO spent most of its life at the Institute, but was hosted at the Divinity School from 1998 to 2002. PONPO is currently directed jointly by the Yale School of Management and the Yale Center for International and Area Studies.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject and personnel files, including computer files, of the Program on Non-Profit Organizations (PONPO) at Yale. The records document all aspects of the program including administration, research, and finance.
Nonprofit organizations -- Research; Research institutes; Yale University. Institution for Social and Policy Studies. Program on Non-Profit Organizations
- Foundation records, 1979-2000; Accession 2004-A-167
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035
  - Access, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AETNA, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 4)
  - Agenzia Federataire, The (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AHSR, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alpha Center (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Can, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Humanics, Inc., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ARDI, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ARNOVA, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19 - 20)
  - Aspen International (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Association of Voluntary Action Scholars, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ATandT (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Atlantic Philanthropic, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Atlantic Richfield Foundation, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25 - 26)
  - B General (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Burness Community (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - C general (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - CBS, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - CE.R.FE, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Center for Global Partnership, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Charities Aid Foundation, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Chevon, USA, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Chicago Community First, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - CIGNA(Connecticut Geberal), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Clarion Conference, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Commercial Activities of Non Profits, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Common Fund (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Conoco (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Continental Group, Inc., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Council for New York Law Associates, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Council on Foundations, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - D General (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Data Inc., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Dentsu Inst. for Human Studies, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Department of State, Wahington DC, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Duke University, Centre for the Study of Philanthropy and Volunteerism, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Egeneral (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Emory University, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Equitable Life/Rudney, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 66 - 67)
  - Exxon Corporation, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Fgeneral (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Ford (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Ford H.S.U.S Grant, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - G general (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - General (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - General Electric, 1981-1988 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - General Mills, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Good Samaritan (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Group Health Associates, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - H general (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Harvard University Press, 1991/92 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Health Administration Press, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Hoffnan-Laroche, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Hospital Fund, Inc., 1989 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - I general (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - IBM, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Independent Research, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 99 - 102)
  - Independent Sector, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 103 - 112)
  - Indiana University, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 113 - 115)
  - International Center for Non-Profit Law, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - International Society for Third-Sector Research, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - J general (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Johnson (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Lorentz Laboratory, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - M Mixed (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Mandel Center, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Mary Goodman Lectureship (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - McArthur, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - McCormack Elizabeth, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Mellon Foundation, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 150 - 151)
  - Merck and Co., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Milbank Quarterly, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Minigrants (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - MIT Social Investment Program, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Monsanto, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Movimento Federation Democratic, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Ngeneral, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 162 - 164)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - National Institute of Education, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - Netherlands Institute for Social Work Research, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - New Haven Foundation, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - New York Community Trust, The (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - New York University (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - New York University (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Non Profit Academic Center Council, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Non Profit Academic Centers Council, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Non Profit Management and Leadership, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - OBER, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Others (Box 7, Folder 182)
  - Oxford University Press, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 183)
  - Philips Hall, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 187)
  - Ponpo Files, History (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - Proposal for the Study of Independent Institutions, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 190)
  - Prudential Bache, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 191)
  - San Fransisco, Univ. of, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - San Fransisco, University of (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - Sasakawa Peace Foundation, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Sloan, 1990-1995 (Box 8, Folder 206)
  - Society for the Advancement of Socio-Economics, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 207)
  - Sun Company Inc. (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Techno Serve, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Texaco/Leadership Development, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - The Harry and Jeanette, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Transaction Books, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Tufts University, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Union Institute (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - United Way of Greater New Haven, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 220)
  - Voluntas International Journal of Voluntary and Non Profit organisations (Box 8, Folder 222)
  - Volunteeer Symposium, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 223)
  - World Health Organisation, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Yale, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 232)
- Working papers and cases in non-profit governance [computer files], 2004; Accession 2004-A-170 (Box 1–2)
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
  - Cases in Non-Profit governance, 19
    General note
    Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
  - Working papers, 244
  - Working papers database, computer file (Excel)
  - Working papers statistics, computer file (Excel)
- Religion project research, circa 1988-2001; Accession 2004-A-195
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - Ammerman, Nancy Tatom; Papers; Religion (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Aspen Institute - A Historical Statistic of the United States, 1997 June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bob Wineberg - New Religion (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bob Wineberg; Papers; Religion Workshop, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Capstone Conference Articles - PONPO, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Carl Milofsky; Paper; Religion Workshop, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Courtney Bender; Papers; Religion Workshop, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Eric M. Uslaner Paper, Religion Workshops (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - John Simon Seminar; Cassette; Transcription, Diskette, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Lilly Leadership Workshop, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Lilly Polity Grant Papers (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Lilly Polity Researcher Reports (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Milofsky, Carl Papers Religion, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - (Papers from)N Jay Demerath, Religion (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - N.J. DemerathIII; Paper; Religion Workshop, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - New Rel: Miriam Wood Project; w/ Melissa Stone, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - New Religion Articles File (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - PDH/Projects: Historical Statistics of the United States; Millenial Edn., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Proof and McKinney, Wade and William Papers, Religion (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Religion Colloquia, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Religion Papers (Box 2, Folder 42 - 43)
  - Religion Project: Research Affiliates (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Supported Publications, PONPO, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Theda Skocpol; New Religion Individual File, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Thomas Ogletree (Dean; Chairman, Advisory Comm.) (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Work in Progress, PONPO, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Brewster Fund records, circa 1977-1998; Accession 2004-A-196
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033
  - Brewster /PONPO Report, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brewster Brochure, PONPO Drafts, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2 - 5)
  - Brewster Drafts and Files (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Brewster Notes (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Brewster Reports (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Brewster, Kingman, Writings of, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Brewster Fund (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Proposals and Publications (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Steering Committee Materials, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Publishing records, circa 1984-1991; Accession 2004-A-198
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2026
  - Basic Books (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Brochure: PONPO (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Relations (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - EDITORS (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Nonprofit Sector(Japanese Translation), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Others (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Publication Blurbs, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Publications List, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Publishers and Publishing Ideas, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - The University Presses (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Working Paper; List and Sale Log (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Yale University Press (source book) (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - General Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Research records concerning Kellog and Lilly, 1990-1997; Accession 2004-A-199
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032
  - AAFRC: Grant Proposal, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee File, Includes "Outline of PONPO General Support Proposal to "Anonymous Donor" (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Financial Budgetary Materials (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Grant Award Letter, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Grant Proposal, A Proposal For Anthology of Readings in the History of American Philanthropy(Peter Hall and Bradford Gray) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lilly - 1998 Public Version (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Capacity building proposal
    - Building Management, Policy, and Leadership Competences in Faith-Based Organizations (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Religion and Public Life in an Era of Institutional Transformation: Implementation Phase (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - New Religion Project Proposal, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - PONPO Annual Reports, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Rel/Mailings, A Guide to Charitable Choice: The Rules of Sect. 104 of the 1996 Federal Welfare Law Governing State Cooperation (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Religion Interim Report, Religion and Public Life in an Era of Institutional Transformation Planning Grant: Interim Report (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Religion Project Proposal(Original), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Religion Project Reports (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Nov. 21 Workshop Originals/Articles (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Religious Project Chron. Files; Jun-Dec 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Seminar files, 1982-2002; Accession 2004-A-200
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2038
  - Announcements, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Seminar, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Announcements
    - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 4)
    - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 6)
    - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8 - 10)
    - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11 - 12)
  - Seminars, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 13 - 15)
  - Seminars, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 16 - 18)
  - PONPO Seminar, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Seminars and Information, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 20 - 24)
  - Early Seminars, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - KMPG/ISPS/PONPO Seminar, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Participant Information, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Participant List, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Presentations; Seminars, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Religion Seminars (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Seminar Binder (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Seminar Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Financial records, 1998-2002; Accession 2005-A-027
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  - AAFRC: Contracts and Grants (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AAFRC: Final Extension/Budget Report (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ARNOVA Reimbursements, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aspen FY (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aspen Grant: Historical Statistics of the United States (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aspen:Financial and Narrative Reports (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Philanthropic Proposed Budget (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Capstone Conference Receipts, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Financial Reports, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 11)
  - Ford, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Gift Account, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 15 - 23)
  - Grants and Contract Adm. - Sally Tremaine, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Grant Full Balance Report, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 25 - 33)
  - Grants - Current Expenses, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Individual Files
  - Kellog
    - Administrative, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - 1999 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - 1999 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Proposal (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - 0107837 1/2001 4/2002 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Grant (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Grants and Contracts, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - 1998 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - 2001 (Box 4, Folder 60 - 62)
    - 2000 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - 2000 Dec (Box 4ii, Folder 64)
  - Lilly Budget Guidelines (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Lilly File Backup (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Lilly Leadership
  - Administrative (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Financial Report, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - 1998 Jan-Dec (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - 1999 April-Dec (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - 2000 Jan-Jun (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Research Money, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Lilly, Reports to, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Lilly Polity
    - 1998 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - 1999 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - 1999 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - 2000, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 83 - 84)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 85 - 89)
    - Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - No date (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Milosfsky Assistants (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - New Religion
    - Expenses, 1996 September - December (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Expenses, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Expenses, 1998 January-March (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Implementation Proposal, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Yale Divinity School, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Budget Reports, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Non Federal Awards, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Other Accounts, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - PIER, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - 1999 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Ponpo Seminar Expenses, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Thomas Jefferson Hospital, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Transactions - Building Management and Maintenance, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 110)
- Administrative records, 1995-1997; Accession 2005-A-028
  - Advisory Committee General Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Committee, PONPO (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brewster, Kingman, 1979/80 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 10 - 13)
  - Curriculum Project, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - International Directory, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Kellog Proposal, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Knauft Meeting, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Management Studies Program, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 28 - 30)
  - MiamiConference, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Minutes, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 36 - 37)
  - New York Times Company Foundation, 1983-1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Other (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Planning: PONPO, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Policy and Management Dilemmas (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Program Description, Topics and Appointments, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Restructuring Committee PONPO/ISPS, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Seven Springs Planning Conference, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- John D. Rockefeller Fellowship records, 1995-1997; Accession 2005-A-029
  - Listing of empty file folders labeled JDR (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 3rd Summer Fellows, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 3rd Summer Fellows, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 3rd Summer Fellows, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 3rd Summer Fellows, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - JDR Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, Jackie, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Various writings and records [computer files], circa 1980-1999; Accession 2005-A-156
  Original computer files, as well as preservation masters, are restriced due to their fragility.. Electronic files cannot be accessed remotely. Copies of the files are available in the repository. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
  - Various PONPO writings and records, Circa 1980 - 1999 (Box 1–5)
    - Schekkan Paper, 2005-A-156-0001; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon: Personal Correspondence, 2005-A-156-0002; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon: personal corresp., 7/83 11/30/83 backup, 2005-A-156-0003; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon: August '82 WAYS & MEANS PROPOSAL for US House of Reps., 2005-A-156-0004; 1 (Box 1)
    - SIMON PERSONAL December 1, 1983 thru April 29, 1984, 2005-A-156-0005; 1 (Box 1)
    - SIMON PERSONA December 1, 1983 thru April 29, 1984 back up copy, 2005-A-156-0006; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon: Personal Corresp. April 30, 1984 thru Sept. 28, 1984 BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0007; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon: Personal Corresp. April 30, 1984 thru Sept. 28 1984, 2005-A-156-0008; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon Correspondence September 28, 1984 thru November 16, 1984 BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0009; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon correspondence September 28, 1984 thru November 16, 1984, 2005-A-156-0010; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon Correspondence November 19, 1984 thru Feb. 12, 1985 BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0011; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon Correspondence November 19, 1984 thru Feb 12, 1985, 2005-A-156-0012; 1 (Box 1)
    - BACKUP Simon Correspondence February 12, 1985 thru May 17, 1985, 2005-A-156-0013; 1 (Box 1)
    - Simon Correspondence February 12, 1985 thru May 17, 1985, 2005-A-156-0014; 1 (Box 1)
    - 1/85 Gannett Proposal (renewal), 2005-A-156-0018; 1 (Box 1)
    - 1/85 Gannett Proposal (renewal) BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0019; 1 (Box 1)
    - Rockefeller Proposal 6/84, Mott Proposal 7/84, 2005-A-156-0023; 1 (Box 1)
    - Rockefeller prop. 6/84, Mott Proposal 7/84, 2005-A-156-0024; 1 (Box 1)
    - RESEARCH REPORTS III articles, etc., 2005-A-156-0025; 1 (Box 1)
    - Research reports mail list disk 02 12/06, 2005-A-156-0026; 1 (Box 1)
    - Participants Lists Ponpoite.lst & List3.dat, 2005-A-156-0027; 1 (Box 1)
    - Address List: Ponpo participants, 2005-A-156-0028; 1 (Box 1)
    - Research Reports Mail List Disk 01 (of 01) 8/11/87, 2005-A-156-0029; 1 (Box 1)
    - Seminar Mail list 2/10/87, 2005-A-156-0030; 1 (Box 1)
    - Backup Adddress list: Ponpo participants, 2005-A-156-0031; 1 (Box 1)
    - Ponpo participants lists backup, 2005-A-156-0032; 1 (Box 1)
    - Applicants (correspondence) May 1985 thru, 2005-A-156-0033; 1 (Box 1)
    - Powelrec.per, 2005-A-156-0034; 1 (Box 1)
    - Personnel (correspondence) 5-85, 2005-A-156-0035; 1 (Box 1)
    - Rudney + mgmt proposals: BACKUP Kellogg, CONOCO, Packard, alcoa, fm, 2005-A-156-0036; 1 (Box 1)
    - backup JM/Rudney 1/85 RS Clark John 3/85, 2005-A-156-0037; 1 (Box 1)
    - JM/Rudney 1/85 RSCLARK fdn 3/85, 2005-A-156-0038; 1 (Box 1)
    - Gen mgmt desc. Management & gov't studies proposal Rudney Studies (Alcoa fdn) DUKE, 2005-A-156-0039; 1 (Box 1)
    - Gen mgmt desc. Management & gov't studies proposal + Rudney Studies (Alcoa fdn) DUKE backup, 2005-A-156-0040; 1 (Box 1)
    - Rudney + mgmt proposals Packard, Kellogg, CONOCO, Texaco, Alcoa, fm, 2005-A-156-0041; 1 (Box 1)
    - Rudney Proposals: Hettinger, Alex Walker, 2005-A-156-0046; 1 (Box 1)
    - Rudney Proposals: Hettinger, Alex Walker BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0047; 1 (Box 1)
    - FDN 1987, 2005-A-156-0048; 1 (Box 1)
    - .PRO 1986-1987, 2005-A-156-0049; 1 (Box 1)
    - .per 1986-1987 3.1, 2005-A-156-0050; 1 (Box 1)
    - .FDN 1986-87, 2005-A-156-0051; 1 (Box 1)
    - .PRO 1987-88 Ford Hewlett, 2005-A-156-0052; 1 (Box 1)
    - .PHASE3 87 3.1, 2005-A-156-0053; 1 (Box 1)
    - .JGS 1986-1987, 1987-, 2005-A-156-0054; 1 (Box 1)
    - .BUD 1986-87 .LOG 1987-, 2005-A-156-0055; 1 (Box 1)
    - Clayton: Company ID & Demo backup 11 pp, 2005-A-156-0056; 1 (Box 1)
    - Levy: A comparison of private and public educational organizations disk one 45 pp. Backup, 2005-A-156-0058; 1 (Box 1)
    - Lecy: Choosing the private-public mix 36pp save 11 pp backup, 2005-A-156-0059; 1 (Box 1)
    - Levy: The private-public question in higher education disk 1 pp backup 45 pp, 2005-A-156-0060; 1 (Box 1)
    - Levy: A comparison of private and public educational organizations disk two 30 pp BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0061; 1 (Box 1)
    - Auld Backups: The Deed of Covenant 4 pages; why (and how) companies give 4 pages, 2005-A-156-0063; 1 (Box 1)
    - Auld: New Haven Case Study (Hawley) Disk one 45 pp. Backup, 2005-A-156-0064; 1 (Box 1)
    - Auld: New Haven Case Study (Hawley) Disk two 4pp. RR#4 Levy 5 pp. Backups, 2005-A-156-0065; 1 (Box 1)
    - Backup: Hawley working paper corporate philanthropy and federal budget cuts, 2005-A-156-0066; 1 (Box 1)
    - James: correspondence backups, 2005-A-156-0067; 1 (Box 1)
    - Stanfield/Auld: pre-world war philanthropy and black america: The case of black higher education 3 pages backup, 2005-A-156-0068; 1 (Box 1)
    - Narrative reports backup disk, 2005-A-156-0069; 1 (Box 2)
    - Program 2 1/2 yr. Narrative (1/1/82-12/31/84), 2005-A-156-0070; 1 (Box 2)
    - Program 2 1/2 yr. Narrative (1/1/82-12/31/84) Backup, 2005-A-156-0071; 1 (Box 2)